

JEAN CARLOS LUCIANO

I would like to consolidate myself in a company that gives me job stability, apply my experiences and knowledge in the different areas of the company, and develops professionally for the good performance of the assigned functions.

CONTACTS

- 581 Academy street 10034 New York New York
- 1-516-738-9735
- jeancarlos3102@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript(Es6, jQuery, AJAX, Vue js AND React JS)
- PostgresSQL, Mysql
- Web Design(Bootstrap, Materialize)
- Codeigniter and Laravel
- Object Oriented PHP
- Node.js
- Office package management, Operating System(PC) and printers.
- ATM Support
- Linux

LANGUAGES

Spanish: native

English:

В1

middle

EDUCATION

INFOTEP, Santiago, Dominican Republic | 10/2015

Technical Support:

Technology

UAPA, Santiago, Dominican Republic

Technical Support:

Technology

EXPERIENCE

Centro Medico Cibao Santiago | 01/2016 - 10/2016

- Computing Manager
- Warehouse Control

United Nearshore Operations (UNO) - Web Developer Santiago | 11/2016 - 07/2018

- Defined and carried out design processes at all levels including research, conceptualization, testing and implementation.
- Redesigned websites to improve navigation and visual appeal.

Diebold Nixdorf - Technical Support (Atm Repair) Santiago | 11/2018 - 08/2019

- Technical Support (Atm Repair)
- Warehouse Control